Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
INCOMING SIGNAL
ALL SYSTEM CHECKED
LOADING...
WEAPON READY
Searching for chemical compound
DETECTED
Not bad for the first time!
The supervisors will be coming.
Go! I'll cover you!
Rebecca.
Ursula!
You shouldn't be here.
But it's always good
to meet you.
She's good but reckless.
This place was too obvious...
She made several mistakes, but
I think she deserves another chance.
No!
Don't fail us again,
Rebecca.
Finish the job.
I trust you. Everything will be fine.
"Rebecca."
DAEMONIUM
Chapter 1: Baptism
Coming soon in DAEMONIUM!
Please rate this subtitle at www.osdb.link/3phtx
Help other users to choose the best subtitles